Mubashar Toseef

Objectives and Goals



To be an active employee who contributes to the Mission, Vision, and Values of the company, and to interact, on a professional level with other Team members. To give an excellent performance, and to transform my experience, knowledge, skills and abilities into Organization's value and Esteem.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Ability to understand/analyses/fulfill customer requirement.
- Good understanding of Electrical Drawings.
- Ability to take ownership of issues and to work alone with little or no supervision.
- Ability to respond to time frames and deadlines with pace.
- Ability to read and interpret wiring diagrams and floor plans.
- Good problem-solving skills for diagnosing electrical faults.
- Both practical as well as theoretical knowledge of Different Electrical Instruments.

PERSONAL

- Good with numbers, and able to use modern computerized tools like MS Office/Email/Internet Browsing, AutoCAD etc.
- Able to communicate effectively at all levels and willing to learn new skills.
- Willing to work on under pressure and target oriented environment.
- Ability to learn quickly is my forte that has helped me successfully manage various jobs given.

CAREER HISTORY

SKA Technology (Sdn. Bhd)

Electrical Supervisor – April, 2017 till August, 2019

Duties:

 Responsible for Installing, maintaining, and repairing electrical wiring, equipment, & fixtures. Making sure that all work done is in accordance with Health & Safety

- regulations. Also involved in advising clients and senior managers verbally or in writing on hazardous equipment and essential work that needs doing.
- Job includes, layout of various types of conduit (RSC, IMC, and PVC coated pipes) both overhead and underground. Installation of cable trays of different sizes and heights.
- To co-ordinate with Electrical Contractor for Electrification, Execution, Erection & Commissioning.
- Control panel mounting/installation and cable layout prior to termination.
- Rectify problems found during preliminary testing.
- Conduct final test of all the system prior to approval of the customer
- Checking & testing circuit breakers and replacing them where required. .
- Tracing, diagnosing and rectifying electrical faults.
- Carrying out electrical installation and maintenance work.
- Carrying out new project work, design and installation.
- Interpreting work instructions, drawings and schematic diagrams.
- Accountable for all electrical and general tasks relating to maintenance.
- Administrative work like maintaining records and files and preparing reports.
- Manage the process of fibre lying ,testing and splicing.
- Carrying out new electrical installation and CCTV.
- To check the entire work as according to approved drawings.

MULTITEK ENGINEERING (Pvt. Ltd)

Electrical Engineer – Feb, 2015 till Jan, 2017

Duties:

- There responsibilities were to troubleshooting of switch gear, perform preventative maintenance.
- Diagnose, locate & fix electrical problems in switchgears.
- Ensure Safety on site and supervise a team of industrial electrician in performing various types of job as per company's scope of work.
- Carrying out new electrical installation.
- Interpreting work instructions, drawings and schematic diagrams.
- Accountable for all electrical and general tasks relating to maintenance.
- Travelling to locations on site and manage both indoor and outdoor.
- Administrative work like maintaining records and files and preparing reports.

Sitara Textile (Pvt. Ltd)

Trainee Engineer (Instrumentation and Maintenance) - 1st Aug, 2013 till 30th Jan, 2014

• Learnt the basic instruments. Their use and installment at industry various areas like Kier scouring & rope Bleaching, stantor machine and preheater, PLC's, control panels and, electric motors etc.

Education and Qualification

Year	Degree/Diploma	University/College	Percentage/Grade
2014	BSc (Electrical Engineering Technology)	GC University Faisalabad	70.85%
2010	DAE (Electrical)	P.B.T.E Lahore	76.36%
2007	Matriculation	B.I.S.E Sargodha	76.82%

Personal Info

S/O : Mubashar Toseef

Citizenship : Pakistani Date of Birth : Oct 31, 1991 Passport No : AA7884322

Driving License No. : Nil

Cell phone No : +92-313-7677677

Personal Email : mubashar.toseef77@gmail.com

Visa Status : Nil

Address : Main Street Pakka Dera Near Istiqlalabad Colony, Sargodha

Languages

English (Fluent)Urdu (Fluent)Malay (Intermediate)

References

Reference will be furnished upon request.